你知道吗, 现实生活就是这样有趣
Real life is a funny thing, you know.
我想我们大多数人都害怕当我们到了生命的尽头时
I think most of us fear reaching the end of our life
回首, 后悔那时候我们没有说出来
and looking back, regretting the moments we didn't speak out.
那些我们没有说我爱你的时刻
When we didn't say I love you.
那些我们应该说对不起的时刻
When we should have say I'm sorry.
所以, 有一段时间的沉默
So there is a time for silence
有一段时间去等待你的机会
and there is a time for waiting your turn.
但是如果你知道你的感受
But if you know how you feel
你如此清楚的知道你要说什么, 你懂的
and you so clearly know what you need to say, you know it.
我觉得你不应该等下去
I don't think you should wait.
你应该现在就说出来
I think you should speak now.
Sparks Fly - Taylor Swift
放下所有的事情吧
Drop everything now
你的每一个动作就好像暴雨旋风一般划过我的心上
The way you move is like a full on rainstorm
而我就像一座纸牌搭起的房子般脆弱, 轻易的被你攻入
And I'm a house of cards
你是那种能让我不计后果迷上的人, 我应该远离
You're the kind of reckless that should send me running
但是我知道, 我就像小磁铁一样离不开磁场
But I kinda know that I won't get far
你就这样站在我的面前
And you stood there in front of me
距离是如此的近, 我可以触碰到你
Just close enough to touch
距离是如此的近, 但愿你不能看清
Close enough to hope you couldn't see
我正在想的事情
What I was thinking of
放下所有的事情吧
Drop everything now
我和你约在瓢泼大雨之中
Meet me in the pouring rain
亲吻在街边的人行道上
Kiss me on the sidewalk
将所有的痛楚都带离了我
Take away the pain
我好像能看见, 当你微笑的时候, 火花正在绽放
Cause' I see sparks fly whenever you smile
宝贝, 你绿色的眼睛就这样得到了我的心
Get me with those green eyes, baby
就好像绚丽的灯光都黯然失色
As the lights go down
当你不在我身边的时候, 有些东西会萦绕于脑际, 难以忘却
Give me something that'll haunt me when you're not around
我好像能看见, 当你微笑的时候, 火花正在绽放
I see, sparks fly whenever you smile
我的理智忘记了提醒我自己
My mind forgets to remind me you're a bad idea
你是一个容易让我入迷的坏念头
You touch me once and it's really something
你会发现我比你想象中的更美好
You find I'm even better than you imagined I would be
我对于外面的世界保持我的小戒心
I'm on my guard for the rest of the world
但是, 和你在一起的时候, 我却毫无防备
But with you I know it's no good
我可以按捺自己的心思, 耐心的等待, 但我希望你能够
And I could wait patiently but I really wish you would
放下所有的事情吧
Drop everything now
我和你约在瓢泼大雨之中
Meet me in the pouring rain
亲吻在街边的人行道上
Kiss me on the sidewalk
将所有的痛楚都带离了我
Take away the pain
我好像能看见, 当你微笑的时候, 火花正在绽放
Cause' I see sparks fly whenever you smile
宝贝, 你绿色的眼睛就这样得到了我的心
Get me with those green eyes, baby
就好像绚丽的灯光都黯然失色
As the lights go down
当你不在我身边的时候, 有些东西会萦绕于脑际, 难以忘却
Give me something that'll haunt me when you're not around
我好像能看见, 当你微笑的时候, 火花正在绽放
I see, sparks fly whenever you smile
我的手指穿过你柔软的头发
I run my fingers through your hair
看着灯火就这样的消失在你的光芒下
And watch the lights go wild
就让你美丽的双眼一直注视着我
Just keep on keeping your eyes on me
这样的错误让我感觉如此美妙
It's just wrong enough to make it feel right
我领上楼梯时
And lead me up the staircase
你会温柔的在我耳边说着悄悄话吗？
Won't you whisper soft and slow
你已经彻底迷住了我的心
I'm captivated by you baby
如同烟火般灿烂于天际
Like a firework show
放下所有的事情吧
Drop everything now
我和你约在瓢泼大雨之中
Meet me in the pouring rain
放下所有的事情吧
Drop everything now
将所有的痛楚都带离了我
Take away take away the pain
放下所有的事情吧
Drop everything now
我和你约在瓢泼大雨之中
Meet me in the pouring rain
放下所有的事情吧
Drop everything now
将所有的痛楚都带离了我
Take away take away the pain
放下所有的事情吧
Drop everything now
我和你约在瓢泼大雨之中
Meet me in the pouring rain
亲吻在街边的人行道上
Kiss me on the sidewalk
将所有的痛楚都带离了我
Take away the pain
我好像能看见, 当你微笑的时候, 火花正在绽放
Cause' I see sparks fly whenever you smile
宝贝, 你绿色的眼睛就这样得到了我的心
Get me with those green eyes, baby
就好像绚丽的灯光都黯然失色
As the lights go down
当你不在我身边的时候, 有些东西会萦绕于脑际, 难以忘却
Give me something that'll haunt me when you're not around
我好像能看见, 当你微笑的时候, 火花正在绽放
I see, sparks fly whenever you smile
宝贝, 火花正在绽放
and sparks fly oh baby
Mine - Taylor Swift
你头也不回的离开了你所生活的那个小镇, 到大学里兼职当餐厅服务生
You were in college, working part time, waiting tables left a small town, never looked back
我当时就是个飞行隐患, 生怕会随时坠落
I was a flight risk, with a fear of falling
想知道为什么我们明知爱不持久却还要继续
Wondering why we bother with love if it never lasts
这叫人如何相信？
I say, Can you believe it?
正当我们两人靠在沙发上
As we're lying on the couch
瞬间我明白了
The moment I could see it
没错, 我现在看清了
Yes, yes, I can see it now
还记得我们曾经坐在水池边吗？
Do you remember, we were sitting there, by the water
你第一次用你的手臂把我紧紧搂住
You put your arm around me for the first time
你变成了我的俘虏
You made a rebel of a careless man's careful daughter
你是我拥有过最好的东西
You are the best thing that's ever been mine
向前倒带, 我们一起乘风破浪
Flash forward and we're taking on the world together
在你家有一个专门放我的东西的抽屉
And there is a drawer of my things at your place
你知道了我的秘密, 也终于懂了我的矜持
You learn my secrets and you figure out why I'm guarded
你说过我们永远不会犯我父母犯过的过错
You said we'd never made my parents' mistakes
但我们有账单要付
But we've got bills to pay
我们什么也没有弄清楚
We got nothing figured out
当我们难以承受的时候
When it was hard to take
没错, 这就是我所烦恼的
Yes, yes, this is what I thought about
还记得我们曾经坐在水池边吗？
Do you remember, we were sitting there, by the water
你第一次用你的手臂把我紧紧搂住
You put your arm around me for the first time
你变成了我的俘虏
You made a rebel of a careless man's careful daughter
你是我拥有过最好的东西
You are the best thing that's ever been mine
还记得当整个城市的灯光在水中浮现吗？
Do you remember all the city lights on the water?
你看到我第一次开始相信
You saw me start to believe for the first time
你变成了我的俘虏
You made a rebel of a careless man's careful daughter
你是我拥有过最好的东西
You are the best thing that's ever been mine
我依然记得我们在凌晨吵的那场架
And I remember that fight, 2:30 a.m.
你说事情全部都失去了我们的控制
You said everything was slipping right out of our hands
我边哭边跑出门, 然而你一直跟着我到街上
I ran out crying, and you followed me out into the street
我硬撑着道了别
Braced myself for the goodbye
因为这就是我所了解的一切
Cause that's all I've ever known
你让我大吃一惊
And you took me by surprise
你说你永远不会让我孤身一人
You said I'll never leave you alone
你说你还记得我们是怎样坐在水池旁的
You said, I remember how we felt sitting by the water
你还说你记得每一次你看着我就像第一次一样
And every time I look at you, it's like the first time
你说你曾经喜欢上一个粗心的爸爸的细心女儿
I fell in love with a careless man's careful daughter
你说我是你拥有过最好的东西
She is the best thing that's ever been mine
我们会走到最后的
(Hold on), we'll make it last
永不回头, 永不后悔
(Hold on, never turn back)
你变成了我的俘虏
(Hold on) You made a rebel of a careless man's careful daughter
你是我拥有过最好的东西
You are the best thing that's ever been mine
你能相信吗？
Do you believe it?
我们会走到最后的
We're gonna make it now
我已经看到我们的未来了
And I can see it
(Yeah, yeah, yeah) (I can see it now)
欧, 芝加哥伊利诺斯州的朋友们, 大家好
Oh hello Chicago, Illinois.
我叫泰勒
My name is Taylor.
欢迎来到爱的告白世界巡回演唱会
And welcome to the Speak Now World Tour.
我说, 今天早些时候, 我正坐在我的化妆室
You know I was sitting in my dressing room a little earlier today.
然后呢
And uh
我听到你们的尖叫声穿过这个混凝土墙
I heard you guys screaming through the concrete walls of this arena.
然后我对自己说...
And I thought to myself ...
我对自己说没有什么反应出这将会是一群很棒的的歌迷
I thought to myself: nothing says this is going to be an amazing crowd
就像能够听到他们的尖叫声穿透混凝土墙
like being able to hear them screaming through concrete walls.
天哪, 我就是
Man I just ...
站在这里望向你们, 我变得如此的着迷
I get so fascinated standing here from this view point.
这里有着今晚能望见每个人的绝佳视野
It's an excellent view of everybody here tonight.
我能看见每一个人
And I can see everyone.
我能看见我最好的朋友都在那边
I can see the best friends who came all laid up over there.
我能看见你们在最上边那里举着'SWIFT'标志的灯
I can see you all the way up of the top with the 'SWIFT' light-up sign.
我还能...
I can...
然后我变得...
And I get ...
我变得对在这里每个人的故事如此地着迷
I get so fascinated by the individual stories in this room.
我是说我想到这个事实
You know I mean I just think about the fact that
你们做了'Long Live'的标志
you guys who made the 'Long Live' sign back there.
那肯定需要好几个小时才能做好
That must have taken hours.
在这里的每个人之前为了今晚能来到这, 都排队等过了很久才能挤进同一个会场
And everyone here who waited in line and piled into the same room to be here tonight.
这对我来说就是如此的令人着迷
It's just so fascinating to me.
我是如此地感激, 因为所有故事里面最重要的
And I am so thankful because the main story of it all
这里最重要的事就是你们13500个人都决定和我一起度过星期五的夜晚
the main story line here is that 13500 of you decide to spend your Friday night with me.
我希望那你们不介意我来告诉你们我的一些故事
And I was hoping you would be alright with you if I would tell you some of my stories.
准备好了吗？
Are you ready?
Go!!!
The Story Of Us - Taylor Swift
我一直这样认为, 在未来的某一天, 我们会这样告诉别人关于我们的故事
I used to think one day we'd tell the story of us
我们眼神第一次交汇和花火悄然绽放的那一瞬间
How we met and the sparks flew instantly
所有人都会说：看, 他们是如此幸运（的找到彼此）
People would say, "they're the lucky ones"
曾经, 我知道我的座位, 一定是紧紧挨着你的那一个
I used to know my place was a spot next to you
现在, 我只能站在那里, 试图找到一个没有人的空位
Now I'm searching the room for an empty seat
最近, 我甚至不知道你在我们这个故事的那一页游荡？
lately I don't even know what page you're on
一个简简单单的复杂
Oh, a simple complication
错误着带领我们远离了爱情
Miscommunications lead to fall out
有好多好多的事情, 我希望你知道
So many things that I wish you knew
有好多好多的阻拦, 我希望我能穿越
So many walls up I can't break through
现在, 我一个人站在这里
Now I'm standing alone
在一个充满欢声笑语的房间里
In a crowded room
你没有说一个字
And we're not speaking
我是如此渴望知道
And I'm dying to know
这伤痛是不是伤害着你
Is it killing you
像汲取我生命一样
Like it's killing me?
自从那些命中注定传说
I don't know what to say
被粉碎
Since a twist of fate
我就已经说不出什么
When it all broke down
那个关于我们的故事
And the story of us
已经宛如悲剧一般
Looks a lot like a tragedy now
下一个篇章
Next chapter
我们是如何让结局变成这样的呢？
How'd we end up this way?
我紧张的不停的拉扯着自己的衣服
See me nervously pulling at my clothes
试图自己看上去忙碌一点
And trying to look busy
你也在尽自己最大的努力躲开我的视线
And you're doing your best to avoid me
我开始这样认为
I'm starting to think one day
我会这样告诉人们, 那个关于我们的故事
I'll tell the story of us
那个关于我是如何将我自己迷失在有你的篇章里
How I was losing my mind when I saw you here
但是你一直紧紧拥抱着自己的自尊, 那应该是你抱紧我的方式
But you held your pride like you should have held me
我害怕看见结局
Oh, we're scared to see the ending
但是为什么我们却假装这一切不算什么
Why are we pretending this is nothing?
我很想告诉你, 我想你, 但是我不知道如何传达我的思念
I'd tell you I miss you but I don't know how
我未曾听见过这般响亮的寂静
I've never heard silence quite this loud
现在, 我一个人站在
Now I'm standing alone
一个充满欢声笑语的房间里
In a crowded room
你没有说一个字
And we're not speaking
我是如此渴望知道
And I'm dying to know
这伤痛是不是伤害着你
Is it killing you
像汲取我生命一样
Like it's killing me?
自从那些命中注定的传说
I don't know what to say
被粉碎
Since a twist of fate
我就已经说不出什么
When it all broke down
那个关于我们的故事
And the story of us
已经宛如悲剧一般
Looks a lot like a tragedy now
我能看见你们跳起来吗
Can I please see you jump?
这好似一场比赛
This is looking like a contest
最能表演出“毫不在乎”的人会赢得最后的奖赏
Of who can act like they care less
但是我却更喜欢有你在我身旁的时光
But I liked it better when you were on my side
战争蓄势待发
The battle's in your hands now
但是, 我会卸下我的盔甲
But I would lay my armor down
如果你更希望这场战争爆发, 那么, 我会拿起我的武器
If you'd say you'd rather love than fight
有好多好多的事情, 你希望我能了解
So many things that you wish I knew
但是, 这个故事的末篇已经拉开的序幕
But the story of us might be ending soon
现在, 我一个人站在
Now I'm standing alone
一个充满欢声笑语的房间里
In a crowded room
你没有说一个字
And we're not speaking
我渴望知道
And I'm dying to know
这伤痛是不是伤害着你
Is it killing you
像汲取我生命一样
Like it's killing me?
自从那些命中注定
I don't know what to say
被粉碎
Since a twist of fate
我就已经说不出什么
When it all broke down
那个关于我们的故事
And the story of us
已经宛如悲剧一般
Looks a lot like a tragedy now, now, now...
你没有说一个字
And we're not speaking
我渴望知道
And I'm dying to know
这伤痛是不是伤害着你
Is it killing you
像汲取我生命一样
Like it's killing me?
自从那些命中注定的幻想
I don't know what to say
被粉碎
Since a twist of fate
我就已经说不出什么
cause we're going down
那个关于我们的故事
And the story of us
已经宛如悲剧一般
Looks a lot like a tragedy now
这个故事, 已经谢幕
The end
Our Song - Taylor Swift
我坐在他车子的副驾驶位子上, 顶着乱糟糟的头发
I was riding shotgun with my hair undone in the front seat of his car
他一只手握着方向盘
He's got a one-hand feel on the steering wheel
另一只手在我心上
The other on my heart
我随意张望, 把收音机的声音关小
I look around, turn the radio down
他说宝贝怎么了？
He says baby is something wrong?
我说没什么, 我只是在想为什么我们没有一首我们的歌
I say nothing I was just thinking how we don't have a song
然后他说...
And he says...
我们的歌是那扇关上的门
Our song is the slamming screen door
当我晚上偷偷溜出去, 敲你的窗户的时候
Sneakin' out late, tapping on your window
是我们讲电话时你悄悄的话语
When we're on the phone and you talk real slow
因为已经是深夜, 并且你妈妈不知道
Cause it's late and your mama don't know
我们的歌是你的笑声
Our song is the way you laugh
第一次约会“天啊, 我没有吻她, 但是我应该吻的”
The first date "man, I didn't kiss her, and I should have"
当我回到家...在我结束祷告前
And when I got home ... before I said amen
问上帝能不能让一切再来一次
Asking God if he could play it again
在一天结束后, 我沿着台阶走进前门廊
I was walking up the front porch steps after everything that day
所有的事都搞砸, 弄得一团糟
Had gone all wrong or been trampled on
被丢弃, 被浪费
And lost and thrown away
通向我可爱的床的途中, 穿过走廊
Got to the hallway, well on my way to my lovin' bed
我几乎没有注意到沿途的玫瑰
I almost didn't notice all the roses
还有那纸条上写着：
And the note that said...
我们的歌是那扇关上的门
Our song is the slamming screen door
当我晚上偷偷溜出去, 敲你的窗户的时候
Sneakin' out late, tapping on your window
是我们讲电话时你悄悄的话语
When we're on the phone and you talk real slow
因为已经是深夜, 并且你妈妈不知道
Cause it's late and your mama don't know
我们的歌是你的笑声
Our song is the way you laugh
第一次约会“天啊, 我没有吻她, 但是我应该吻的”
The first date "man, I didn't kiss her, and I should have"
当我回到家...在我结束祷告前
And when I got home ... before I said amen
问上帝能不能让一切再来一次
Asking God if he could play it again
我听了每一张专辑, 听了收音机
I've heard every album, listened to the radio
等待着某些事情发生
Waited for something to come along
这种感觉很好, 就像我们的歌一样...
That was as good as our song...
因为我们的歌是那扇关上的门
Cause our song is the slamming screen door
当我晚上偷偷溜出去, 敲他的窗户的时候
Sneaking out late, tapping on his window
是我们讲电话时他悄悄的话语
When we're on the phone and he talks real slow
因为已经是深夜, 并且他妈妈不知道
Cause it's late and his mama don't know
我们的歌是他的笑声
Our song is the way he laughs
第一次约会“天啊, 我没有吻她, 但是我应该吻的”
The first date "man, I didn't kiss her, man I should have"
当我回到家...在我结束祷告前
And when I got home ... before I said amen
问上帝能不能让一切再来一次
Asking God if he could play it again...
我坐在他车子的副驾驶位子上, 顶着乱糟糟的头发
I was riding shotgun with my hair undone in the front seat of his car
我拿起一支钢笔和一条旧餐巾
I grabbed a pen and an old napkin
然后写下我们的歌
And I... wrote down our song
你们真的叫的好大声
You guys are really really loud.
哇！！！
Wow!!!
我喜欢这样。我喜欢和你们一起呆着
I love it. I love hanging out with you guys
就因为你们吼声大, 你们会和我一起跳舞, 你们知道所有的歌词
because you're loud and you're daning and you know all the words
并且你们人非常非常好, 这点我很感激
and you're also very very nice which I appreciate.
你们就是好
You guys are.
你们这样好对我来说意义真的很大
You know the nice thing you guys being nice really means a lot to me
因为在我生命当中, 我遇到过这种人
because in my lifetime I've run into people who
他们没你们这么好
aren't quite as nice.
其实他们更加卑鄙
They're in fact more mean.
Mean - Taylor Swift
你, 带着你那好似刀
You, with your words like knives
剑一般犀利话语来伤害着我
and swords and weapons that you use against me
你, 曾经好不留情的把我撞倒两次
You, have knocked me off my feet again
让我失去的知觉
Got me feelin' like a nothing
你, 用着你那好似指甲在黑板上划着一般刺耳的声音
You, with your voice like nails on a chalkboard
在我轻轻呼吸的时候大声喊叫着
Callin' me out when I'm wounded
你, 捉弄着一个弱势的人
You, pickin' on the weaker man
你可以用一阵轻柔微风, 将我吹倒
You can take me down with just one single blow
但是, 你不知道, 你真的不知道
But you don't know what you don't know
总有一天, 我会住在一个让人大呼“棒极了”的城市
Someday I'll be livin' in a big ole city
而你将得到的只是, 无止尽的卑鄙
And all you're ever gonna be is mean
总有一天, 我会变的足够强壮, 这样你就不能再伤害到我
Someday I'll be big enough so you can't hit me
而你将得到的只是, 无止尽的卑鄙
And all you're ever gonna be is mean
为什么你如此卑鄙？
Why you gotta be so mean?
你, 你那两头倒的墙头草
You, with your switching sides
你那如野火般散布的谎言, 还有你的羞辱
And your wildfire lies and your humiliation
你, 又一次的指出我的不足之处
You, have pointed out my flaws again
就好像我没有看见它们一样
As if I don't already see them
我, 低下我的头经过你的面前
I walk with my head down
不想让你看见我, 因为我没有办法在你脑海中留下好印象
Tryna block you out 'cause I never impress you
我仅仅想找回以前那种”不错”的感觉
I just wanna feel okay again
我真希望, 你会被四处攻击
I bet you got pushed around
有人可以让你感到刺骨钻心的寒冷
Somebody made you cold
但是, 就让这个无止尽的来回就此了结吧
But the cycle ends right now
因为你没有办法让我变得和一你样卑鄙
Cause you can't lead me down that road
你不知道, 你真的不知道
And you don't know what you don't know
总有一天, 我会住在一个让人直呼“棒极了”的城市
Someday I'll be livin' in a big ole city
而你将得到的只是, 无止尽的卑鄙
And all you're ever gonna be is mean
总有一天, 我会变得足够的强壮, 让你没有办法伤害到我
Someday I'll be big enough so you can't hit me
而你将得到的只是, 无止尽的卑鄙
And all you're ever gonna be is mean
为什么你一定要这样卑鄙呢？
Why you gotta be so mean?
我已经可以预见几年后的你, 坐在路口角落的酒吧里
And I can see you years from now in a bar
和路人讨论着正在上演的橄榄球
Talkin' over a football game
你大声的说着你的想法, 但是
With that same big loud opinion but
没有人在听
Nobody's listening
筋疲力尽却还怒气冲冲地叫嚷着不值得一提的往事
Washed up and ranting about the same old bitter things
醉醺醺的嘟囔着你认为我是如何不会唱歌
Drunk and rumbling on about how I can't sing
你真的很卑鄙
All you are is mean
你的生活真的是, 卑鄙
谎话连篇
And a liar
可悲的
And pathetic
孤单一人
And alone in life
真是卑鄙, 卑鄙, 卑鄙, 还有, 卑鄙
And mean, and mean, and mean, and mean
总有一天, 我会住在一个让人直呼“棒极了”的城市
But someday I'll be livin' in a big ole city
而你将得到的只是, 无止尽的卑鄙
And all you're ever gonna be is mean, yeah
总有一天, 我会变得足够的强壮, 让你没有办法伤害到我
Someday I'll be big enough so you can't hit me
而你将得到的只是, 无止尽的卑鄙
And all you're ever gonna be is mean
为什么你一定要这样卑鄙呢？
Why you gotta be so mean?
总有一天, 我会住在一个让人直呼“棒极了”的城市
Someday I'll be livin' in a big old city
而你将得到的只是, 无止尽的卑鄙
And all you're ever gonna be is mean
(为什么你一定要这样卑鄙呢？)
(Why you gotta be so mean?)
总有一天, 我会变得足够的强壮, 让你没有办法伤害到我
Someday I'll be big enough so you can't hit me
而你将得到的只是, 无止尽的卑鄙
And all you're ever gonna be is mean
为什么你一定要这样卑鄙呢？
Why you gotta be so mean?
Back To December, Apologize, You're Not Sorry - Taylor Swift
我真的很高兴你能抽出时间来看我
I'm so glad you made time to see me
最近怎么样呢？告诉我吧, 你的家人都怎么样呢？
How's life? Tell me, how's your family?
我已经很久没有看见他们了
I haven't seen them in a while
你最近过的不错, 比以前忙了许多
You've been good, busier than ever
我们简短的谈论着工作和天气
Small talk: work and the weather
你开始警惕起来, 我知道为什么
Your guard is up and I know why
因为你还清楚的记得,
Because the last time you saw me will still
上一次, 我对你的伤害
burn in the back of your mind
你送给我玫瑰, 我却没有珍惜的让她们就这样消逝
You gave me roses and I left them there to die
我把自己的骄傲吞到肚子里
So this is me swallowing my pride
站在你的面前, 说道对于那一晚, 我真的对不起
Standin' in front of you, sayin' I'm sorry for that night
我一直试图回到那个十二月
And I go back to December all the time
自由了, 剩下的却只有想念你
It turns out freedom aint nothin' but missin' you
我真的希望我能在那个时候意识到自己做了什么
Wishin' I'd realized what I had when you were mine
我回到那个十二月, 改变一切把所有是事情都变成正确的
I go back to December, turn around and make it alright
我一直都试图回到那个十二月
I go back to December all the time
最近, 我一直辗转无眠
These days I haven't been sleepin'
彻夜回想, 在你生日的那一天
Stayin' up playin' back myself leavin'
我就是这样的离开, 我没有打电话给你
When your birthday passed and I didn't call
我一直都在回忆着夏天, 那些美好的时光
And I think about summer, all the beautiful times
我坐在副驾驶的位置上, 看着你的笑脸
I watched you laughin' from the passenger side and
秋天来临时, 我是如此的爱你
I realized I loved you in the fall
然后, 寒冷就这样袭来, 黑暗的日子
And then the cold came, the dark days
当恐惧就这样潜入我的心里
When fear crept into my mind
你给了我你所有的爱, 我给你的却是 再见
You gave me all your love and all I gave you was goodbye
我把自己的骄傲吞到肚子里
So this is me swallowing my pride
站在你的面前, 说道对于那一晚, 我真的对不起
Standin' in front of you, sayin' I'm sorry for that night
我一直试图回到那个十二月
And I go back to December all the time
自由了, 剩下的却只有想念你
It turns out freedom aint nothin' but missin' you
我真的希望我能在那个时候意识到自己做了什么
Wishin' I'd realized what I had when you were mine
我回到那个十二月
I go back to December
改变一切, 改变自己的想法
Turn around and change my own mind
我一直试图回到那个十二月
I go back to December all the time
我想念你略带褐色的皮肤, 你甜蜜的微笑
I miss your tan skin, your sweet smile
你对我是那么的好
So good to me, so right
还有在那个九月的夜晚, 你是如何把我挽入你的怀中
And how you held me in your arms that September night
你第一次看见我哭泣
The first time you ever saw me cry
也许这是一个梦想般的假设
Maybe this is wishful thinking
一个没头没脑的梦想
Probably mindless dreaming
如果我们能够再爱一次, 我发誓我会真的爱你
If we loved again I swear I'd love you right
我会选择回到那个时间, 改变一切。但是我不能
I'd go back in time and change it but I can't
如果你的心门对我紧锁着, 我能理解
So if the chain is on your door, I understand
然后你说
And you said
现在说对不起已是太迟, 真的太迟
It's too late to apologize, it's too late
你说过现在说对不起已是太迟, 真的太迟
You said it's too late to apologize, it's too late
我把自己的骄傲吞到肚子里
This is me swallowing my pride
站在你的面前, 说道对于那一晚, 我真的对不起
Standin' in front of you, sayin' I'm sorry for that night
我回到那个十二月,
And I go back to December
自由了, 剩下的却只有想念你
It turns out freedom aint nothin' but missin' you
我真的希望我能在那个时候意识到自己做了什么
Wishin' I'd realized what I had when you were mine
你说你不是真心对不起
You said you're not sorry, no oh no oh
你不是真心对不起
And you're not sorry, no oh no oh
Hey you're not sorry, no oh no oh
嗨, 是我, 请留言
Hey, it's me, leave a message, make it hot
现在自己到角落站着好好想想你都做了什么
Now go stand in the corner and think about what you did
Better Than Revenge - Taylor Swift
我们的故事开始于 在那年夏天结束的时候
The story starts when it was hot and it was summer
曾经, 我拥有一切, 我拥有梦寐以求的他
And, I had it all; I had him right there where I wanted him
她就这样闯入了我们的世界, 带走了他。让我们来听听那些响起的掌声吧
She came along, got him along, and let's hear the applause
她带走他的速度比你说完“第三者破坏法”还快
She took him faster than you can say sabotage
我不曾怀疑, 也不曾料想到事情会这样发生,
I never saw it coming, nor did I suspected it
我实在是太低估了, 她, 这个我正在对付的人
I underestimated just who I was dealing with
她应该知道她带来的伤痛, 好像把我当成鼓一般的疯狂敲击
She had to know the pain was beating on me like a drum
她也低估了我, 这个她正在从我这里偷取的人
She underestimated just who she was stealing from
她不是圣人, 她不是你认为的那样完美
She's not a saint and she's not what you think
她只是一个演员
She's an actress, Whoa
她做的那些事让她变得有名
She's better known for the things that she does
“床垫上的那些事”
On the mattress, Whoa
不久之后, 她就会发现
Soon she's gonna find
在操场窃取别人“玩具”
Stealing other people's toys on the playground
并不会让你交到更多的朋友
Won't make you many friends
她应该记住
She should keep in mind
她应该牢牢的记住
我不能做出任何比复仇更好的事情了
There is nothing I do better than revenge, Ha
她的生活好像派对不断, 总能在宾客名单上看见她的名字
She lives her life like it's a party and she's on the list
她看着我, 就好象我还被“那件事”影响着, 而她已经彻底摆脱了一样
She looks at me like I'm a trend and she's so over it
我认为她一直紧皱着眉头会是一个小麻烦
I think her ever present frown is a little troubling
她认为我有心理问题
And, she thinks I'm psycho
因为我喜欢把她的名字和一些东西押韵的并排在一起
Cause I like to rhyme her name with things, but
但是复杂巧妙的世故, 并不得意于你的穿着, 或你认识那些“人”
Sophistication isn't what you wear, or who you know
也不是你把别人踩在脚底下只为让自己爬的更高
Or pushing people down to get you where you wanna go
难道他们在幼稚园的时候没有教导过你吗
Oh they didn't teach you that in prep school
所以, 现在我来决定一切
So it's up to me
那些典雅的裙子并没有给你高贵的气质
But no amount of vintage dresses gives you dignity
她不是圣人, 她不是你认为的那样完美
She's not a saint and she's not what you think
她只是一个演员
She's an actress, Whoa
她做的那些事让她变得有名
She's better known for the things that she does
“床垫上的那些事”
On the mattress, Whoa
不久之后, 她就会发现
Soon she's gonna find
在操场上窃取别人“玩具”
Stealing other people's toys on the playground
并不会让你交到更多的朋友
Won't make you many friends
应该记住
She should keep in mind
她应该牢牢的记住
我不能做出任何比复仇更好的事情了
There is nothing I do better than revenge
亲爱的, 我只是一件让你揉揉眼睛就过去的小事
I'm just another thing for you to roll your eyes at honey
你也许能够得到他, 但是, 你没有听说吗？
You might have him, but haven't you heard
亲爱的, 我只是一件让你揉揉眼睛就过去的小事
I'm just another thing for you to roll your eyes at honey
你也许能够得到他, 但是我会是那一个微笑到最后的那一个
You might have him, but I always get the last word
喔
Whoa
她不是圣人, 她不是你认为的那样完美
She's not a saint and she's not what you think
她只是一个演员
She's an actress, Whoa
她做的那些事让她变得有名
She's better known for the things that she does
“床垫上的那些事”
On the mattress, Whoa
不久之后, 她就会发现
Soon she's gonna find
在操场上窃取别人“玩具”
Stealing other people's toys on the playground
并不会让你交到更多的朋友
Won't make you many friends
她应该记住
She should keep in mind
她应该牢牢的记住
我不能做出任何比复仇更好的事情了
There is nothing I do better than revenge
And do you still feel like you know what you're doing
我并不认为你知道
Cause I don't think you do, Oh
你还固执的认为, 你知道你犯下的错误吗？
Do you still feel like you know what you're doing
我不认为你知道, 你真的不知道
I don't think you do, I don't think you do
就让那些掌声来传达
Let's hear the applause
你确实应该得到一些掌声
See you deserve some applause
因为你真的比以前好了很多
Cause you're so much better
她带走他的速度比你说完“第三者破坏法”还快
She took him faster than you can say sabotage
Speak Now - Taylor Swift
我, 不是那样的女孩
I am not the kind of girl
那样, 随随便便的就闯进
Who should be rudely barging in
雪白圣洁的教堂
On a white veil ocassion
你, 也不是那样的男孩
But you are not the kind of boy
那样, 随随便便的和一个人携手一生
Who should be marrying the wrong girl
我悄悄的溜了进来, 你的朋友们都在
I sneak in and see your friends
还有, 她的那些家人们, 打扮的好似蜡像一般, 好不自然
And her snotty little family all dressed in pastells
而你的她, 正穿着包不住陷的酥皮点心一样的礼服,
And she is yelling at a bridesmaid
在某一个角落, 对着伴娘大吼大叫
Somewhere back inside a room wearing a gown shaped like a pastry
这, 一定不是你曾经幻想中的画面吧
Thiiiiis iiis surely not what you thought it would be
我, 一定是把自己迷失在了梦境里
IIIIIII lose myself in a daydream
直冲了进去, 说道
Burst in and say
“不要说我愿意, 快点逃走吧”
Don't say yes runaway now
“当你离开教堂的时候,
I'll meet you when you're out
我会在小草丛生的后门等你”
of the church at the back door
“不要等待, 也不要说誓言里的一个字”
Don't wait or say a single vow
“你需要听我把话说完”
You need to hear me out
当我还有机会的时候
And they said speak now
婚礼应有的欢乐, 正悄然变化着
Fun gestures are exchanged
管风琴的乐声
And the organ starts to play
也演变成了死亡进行曲
A song that sounds like a death march
我把自己隐藏在了帘幕的后面
And I am hiding in the curtains
看起来, 我并没有被那个“可爱的”“即将成为你新娘”的人邀请
It seems that I was uninvited by your lovely bride-to-be
她, 经过来宾的时候, 像个选美皇后似的, 骄傲的仰着下巴
Sheeee floats down the aisle like a pagent queen
但是, 我知道你希望, 那个人, 是我
But IIIIII knooooow you wish it was me
你希望, 即将牵着的, 是我的手
You wish it was me
难道不是吗？
Don't you
“不要说我愿意, 快点逃走吧”
Don't say yes runaway now
“当你离开教堂的时候,
I'll meet you when you're out
我会在后面的小门等你”
of the church at the back door
“不要等待, 也不要说誓言里的一个字”
Don't wait or say a single vow
“你需要听我把话说完”
You need to hear me out
当我还有机会的时候
And they said speak now
“不要说我愿意, 快点逃走吧”
Don't say yes runaway now
“当你离开教堂的时候,
I'll meet you when you're out
我会在小草丛生的后门等你”
of the church at the back door
“不要等待, 也不要说誓言里的一个字”
Don't wait or say a single vow
时间正一点一滴的流逝
Your time is running out
这一刻, 还是有机会的时候
And they said speak now
牧师庄重的声音响起
I hear the preacher say
“有意见的人, 请现在说吧。不然, 请不要再提起, 直到地老天荒”
Speak now or forever hold your peace
寂静淹没了一切
There's the silence
这是我最后的机会了
There's my last chance
我, 站了起来, 手不停的晃动着
I stand up with shaking hands
眼光, 都洒在了我的身上
All eyes on me
教堂里每个人都惊讶的看着我
Horrified looks from everyone in the room
但是, 我却只是, 望着你
But I'm only lookin at you
我, 不是那样的女孩
I am not the kind of girl
那样, 随随便便就闯进
Who should be rudely barging in
雪白圣洁的教堂
On a white veil ocassion
你, 也不是那样的男孩
But you are not the kind of boy
那样, 随随便便的和一个人携手一生
Who should be marrying the wrong girl
“不要说我愿意, 快点逃走吧”
Don't say yes runaway now
“当你离开教堂的时候
I'll meet you when you're out
我会在小草丛生的后门等你”
of the church at the back door
“不要等待, 也不要说誓言里的一个字”
Don't wait or say a single vow
“你需要听我把话说完”
You need to hear me out
当我还有机会的时候
And they said speak now
然后, 你会告诉我“让我们一起逃离这里吧”
And you'll say let's run away now
“当我脱下礼服的时候, 我会去教堂后面那个小门见你”
I'll meet you when I'm out of my tux at the back door
“亲爱的, 我没有说那誓言上的一个字”
Baby I didn't say my vows
真的好幸运, 当我们还有机会的时候, 你在我的身边。
So glad you were around when they said speak now
“让我们一起逃走吧”
Let's runaway now
“亲爱的, 我没有说那誓言上的一个字”
Baby I didn't say my vows
真的好幸运, 当我们还有机会的时候, 你在我的身边。
So glad you were around when they said speak now
你们真是令人难以置信
You guys are absolutely unbelievable.
就像我想的一样
It's like I'm imaging you.
你们太不可思议了
You got amazing. Thank you
我说
You know
我觉得
I think uh
我觉得在我的脑海
I think in my mind
我有点喜欢把不同的乐器分类到具有不同情感色彩的声音当中, 就像
I kinda categorize different instruments a sounding like different emotions like
就像, 额
like uh
比如对我来说, 大提琴听起来很悲伤
for example like for me a cello sounds sad
然后我正在弹的这个夏威夷四弦琴听起来很欢快, 你觉得呢？
and uh a ukulele I'm playing right now that sounds really happy ,don't you think
这是我几年前在夏威夷弄到的
I got this in howaii a few years ago and uh...
我一直想在演唱会给你们演奏
I've always wanted to play for you in a concert
但感觉
But it felt like...
感觉如果我要为你们演奏, 我必须演奏演奏一首欢快的歌曲, 你们觉得呢？
it felt like if I was gonna play it for you I'd have to
play it on a very happy song, don't you think
就像一首关于坠入爱河或是第一次度过人生当中最好的一天的歌曲
You know like a song about falling in love or having a best first day of your entire life
你懂的, 就那些事（不知道是不是我想的那些事 r(s3t)q）
you know things like that
因为我感觉, 感觉那些事不只让你觉得高兴
because I feel like I feel like those things not only make you feel happy
它们还让你感到无所畏惧
but they also make you feel fearless
Fearless, I'm Yours, Hey, Soul Sister - Taylor Swift
我们的路上, 有很多景致
Somethin'bout the way
小道看起来像刚被雨打湿
The street looks when it's just rained
人行道的条纹反着光
There's a glow off the pavement
你和我走到车前
You walk me to the car
但你知道么, 我想请你和我跳一支舞, 就在这里
And you know I wanna ask you to dance right there
在这停车场的中心
In the middle of the parking lot
耶
Yeah
嘿, 嘿, 嘿~
Hey, hey, hey~ (hey, soul sister)
沿着路行驶
Drivin' down the road
想知道你是否有察觉
Wonder if you know
我用尽全身力气地不想这么快被你迷住
I'm tryin' so hard not to get caught up now
你的一举一动都散发着魅力
You're just so cool
你把手从发间穿过
Run your hands through your hair
不经意的动作, 却让我抵抗不了你
Absent mindedly makin' me want you
没有什么事会让我觉得比这更美好了
And I don't know how it gets better than this
你拉着我的手, 不回头地向前跑
You take my hand and drag me head first
我不怕冒险
Fearless
不知道是为什么, 和你在一起我可以舞蹈
And I don't know why but with you I'd dance
穿着我最精致的裙子, 哪怕是在暴风雨中
In a storm in my best dress
我不怕冒险
Fearless
宝贝请开的慢些
So baby drive slow
直到我们离开了这个小镇的大道
Till we run out of road in this one horse town
我多么想一直坐在你旁边的座位
I wanna stay right here in this passenger's seat
你用你的眼睛深深地望着我
You put your eyes on me
现在加州已经捕捉了所有记忆
Californian now capture every memory
没有什么事会让我觉得比这更美好了
And I don't know how it gets better than this
你拉着我的手, 不回头地向前跑
You take my hand and drag me head first
我不怕冒险
Fearless
不知道是为什么, 和你在一起我可以舞蹈
And I don't know why but with you I'd dance
穿着我最精致的裙子, 哪怕是在暴风雨中
In a storm in my best dress
我不怕冒险
Fearless
我绝不, 绝不再犹豫
I won't hesitate no more, no more (I'm yours)
一刻也不能再等, 我是你的
It cannot wait, I'm yours(I'm yours)
嘿, 嘿, 嘿~
Hey, hey, hey~ (hey, soul sister)
因为没有什么事会让我觉得比这更美好了
Cauz I don't know how it gets better than this
你拉着我的手, 不回头地拽着我向前跑
You take my hand and drag me head first
我不怕冒险
Fearless
不知道是为什么, 和你在一起我可以舞蹈
And I don't know why but with you I'd dance
穿着我最精致的裙子, 哪怕是在暴风雨中
In a storm in my best dress
我不怕冒险
Fearless
当我12岁左右时, 我开始写歌
When I started writing songs when I was about 12
然后额
And uh
你知道那时候
you know back then
那最初更有点像是一种爱好
it kind of started out something that was like more of a hobby
我真的喜欢写歌
I really liked doing it
然后写歌变成一种每日放学后的活动
And then it became something that was like a daily after-school activity
再然后写歌变成所有我曾想做的事
And then it became all that I ever wanted to do
所有我曾梦想的事
all I ever thought about dreamed about
它完完全全变成我的一切
It became absolutely everything to me
我从心底里感谢你们
And I thank you from the bottom of my heart
为使得一些事对我来说意义重大, 你们为我创造的一条歌唱事业道路
for making something that means that much to me, a career path
我倾向于写一些关于爱情和关系的歌
I... uh I tend to write a lot of songs about love and relationships that tends to be
那些都是歌的主题
the main topic covered
我觉得这是因为
And I think it's because
当我们强烈地感受到一些事的时候, 我们最需要音乐来表达
we need music the most when we're feeling things really intensely
我觉得你生命当中最深刻的是
And I think the most intense times in your life are
当你陷入爱河或者分手的时候
when you're either falling in love or losing it
你们觉得呢
Don't you think
我觉得
And I think...
我觉得我应该归入绝望的浪漫主义那一类
I think I fall into the category of the hopeless romantics
我觉得你们也是
And I think you do too
因为你们也在这里
because you're here
我明白了一些事
I see the things
关于我们的极其微妙的事
the tricky thing about us
关于绝望的浪漫主义的极其微妙的事就是
the tricky thing about the hopeless romantics is that
当我们爱上某人
when we fall in love with someone
当我们打招呼的时候
when we say hello
这是神奇的
and it's magical
我们从没想象过某天问候可能变成最后的见面
We never imagined that hello could someday turn into a goodbye
当我们第一次接吻的时候
And when we have first kiss with someone
这是神奇的
and it's magical
我们从没
We never
从没
ever
想象过某天那可能变成最后一次亲吻
imagine that someday that could turn into a last kiss
Last Kiss - Taylor Swift
我依旧记得你脸上的表情
I still remember the look on your face
点亮了凌晨1点58分的夜空
Lit through the darkness at 1:58
那些耳边轻轻划过的, 你说的悄悄话
The words that you whispered
那是我们之间的小秘密
For just us to know
你告诉我, 你爱过我
You told me you loved me
那就请告诉我, 你为什么要离开
So why did you go
去了很遥远的地方
Away
我寻回了我的记忆
I do recall now
我记得那雨滴的味道
The smell of the rain
好像一秒前, 才降落到路面上般晶莹剔透
Fresh on the pavement
我逃离了那架即将离开地面的飞机
I ran off the plane
那个七月的第九天
That July 9th
我能感受到你心的跳动
The beat of your heart
即使在厚厚的外衣的包裹下
It jumps through your shirt
依旧能感受到你臂膀带来的温暖
I can still feel your arms
但是, 现在, 我独自一人, 坐在地板上
But now I'll go sit on the floor
穿着残留你气味的衣服
Wearing your clothes
我所知道的是
All that I know is
我不知道怎么样才能成为, 你会怀念的那一个
I don't know how to be something you miss
不曾想过, 那会是我们最后的一个吻
Never thought we'd have a last kiss
不曾料到 , 我们的结局尽会是这样
I never imagined we'd end like this
你的名字, 永远留于我的唇齿之间
Your name, forever the name on my lips
我清楚的记得
I still remember
你步调的摆动
The swing in your step
在生活这场派对里, 又一次的成功的炫耀着
The life of the party, you're showing off again
我揉了一揉我的眼睛
And I roll my eyes and then
然后, 你拉我进入这场舞会
You pull me in
我不是一个喜欢跳舞的女孩
I'm not much for dancing
但是, 为了你, 我在脚底开出花朵
But for you I did
因为, 我爱上了
Because I love your handshake
你和我父亲握手的方式
Me and my father
我爱上了, 你走路时总是把手放在口袋里的样子
I love how you walk with your hands in your pockets
你是如何在我喋喋不休的时候突然吻我
How you kissed me when I was in the middle of saying something
没有一天, 我不怀念这个“粗鲁的打断方式”
There's not a day when I don't miss those rude interruptions
但是, 现在, 我独自一人坐在地板上
But now I'll go sit on the floor
穿着残留着你气味的衣服
Wearing your clothes
我所知道的是
All that I know is
我不知道怎么样才能成为, 你会怀念的那一个
I don't know how to be something you miss
不曾想过, 那会是我们最后的一个吻
Never thought we'd have a last kiss
不曾料到 , 我们的结局尽会是这样
Never imagined we'd end like this
你的名字, 永远留于我的唇齿之间
Your name, forever the name on my lips
现在, 我只能看着照片里的你, 想象着我还像以前一样偷偷的看你睡着的样子
So I'll watch you live in pictures like I used to watch you sleep
我感受着你忘记我的方式, 就好像以前我感受着你的呼吸
And I feel you forget me like I used to feel you breathe
我一直和我们以前的朋友保持着联系, 只是为了能从他们那里知道, 你最近过的好不好
And I keep up with our old friends just to ask them how you are
希望你在一个很美妙的地方
Hope it's nice where you are
希望那里的阳光都是温柔的
And I hope the sun shines
希望是一个好天气
And it's a beautiful day
希望有一些东西, 能够让你想起
And something reminds you
你曾经希望你还在我身边
You wish you had stayed
你可以改变天气, 可以改变地点
You can plan for a change in weather and town
但是, 我从未想过你会改变你的心
But I never planned on you changing your mind
但是, 现在, 我独自一人坐在地板上
So I'll go sit on the floor
穿着你残留着你气味的衣服
Wearing your clothes
我所知道的是
All that I know is
我不知道怎么样才能成为, 你会怀念的那一个
I don't know how to be something you miss
不曾想过, 那会是我们最后的一个吻
Never thought we'd have a last kiss
不曾料到 , 我们的结局尽会是这样
I never imagined we'd end like this
你的名字, 永远留于我的唇齿之间
Your name, forever the name on my lips
就像我们最后的一个吻
Just like our last kiss
永远留于我的唇齿之间
Forever the name on my lips
就像我们的结局
Just like our last
你们这里有很多令人惊叹的乐队
You know you guys have a lot of amazing bands from this part of the world.
你们知道吗？
Did you know that?
Drops Of Jupiter - Taylor Swift
他已从神奇的太空之旅归来
Now that he's back in the atmosphere
秀发上带着木星（丘比特）的眼泪
With drops of Jupiter in his hair, hey, hey
他夏日般的热情和风雨般的步伐
He acts like summer and walks like rain
令我感到了时光的流逝
Reminds me that there's time to change, hey, hey
他从月球归来后
Since the return from his stay on the moon
像春天一般的聆听, 像六月一样健谈
He listens like spring and he talks like June, hey, hey
告诉我, 你是否穿越了太阳的光辉
Tell me did you sail across the sun
是否看到了银河, 是否找到了星光消逝的地方
Did you make it to the Milky Way to see the lights all faded
也许天堂真的只是一个虚无缥缈的梦想
And that heaven is overrated
告诉我, 你是否爱上了一颗流星
Tell me, did you fall for a shooting star
没有永恒伤疤的流星
One without a permanent scar
当你在星空中寻求自我的时候, 是否想到了我
And did you miss me while you were looking for yourself out there
他结束了完美的太空假日
Now that he's back from that soul vacation
正在归途中穿越星座
Tracing his way through the constellation, hey, hey
他边听莫扎特边练跆拳道
He checks out Mozart while she does tae-bo
令我感叹时光的交错
Reminds me that there's a wound to grow, hey, hey
现在这个连星际旅行都经历过的他
Now he's back in the atmosphere
我真的很害怕, 他会认为我是一个胆小的懦夫
I'm afraid that he might think of me as plain ol' Jane
她会说我从来没有飞翔的胆量, 也永远不会体验到着陆的快感
Told a story about a man who was too afraid to fly so he never did land
告诉我, 风儿是否令你倾心
Tell me did the wind sweep you off your feet
你是否得以和日出之光共舞
Did you finally get the chance to dance along the light of day
一起回到了那灿烂的银河
And head back to the Milky Way
金星（维纳斯）的美丽是否带给了你惊喜
And tell me, did Venus blow your mind
这一切是否实现了你所有的梦想
Was it everything you wanted to find
当你在星空中寻求自我的时候, 是否想到了我
And did you miss me while you were looking for yourself out there
你能想像这样的生活吗：没有爱, 没有自豪, 没有油炸鸡块
Can you imagine no love, pride, deep-fried chicken
即使有时我知道你是错的
Your best friend always sticking up for you
你最好的朋友, 还总是和你站在一起
Even when I know you're wrong
你能想像你没有了与爱人的第一次共舞
Can you imagine no first dance
没有了浪漫的情调, 没有了五个小时的电话缠绵
Freeze dried romance five-hour phone conversation
你没有了曾经拥有的最好的咖啡, 没有了我
The best soy latte that you ever had and . . . me
告诉我, 风儿是否令你倾心
Tell me did the wind sweep you off your feet
你是否得以和日出之光共舞
Did you finally get the chance to dance along the light of day
一起回到了那灿烂的银河
And head back to the Milky Way
告诉我, 你是否爱上了一颗流星
Tell me, did you fall for a shooting star
一颗没有永恒伤疤的流星
One without a permanent scar
当你在星空中寻求自我的时候, 是否想到了我
And did you miss me while you were looking for yourself
呐 呐 呐 ...
Na na na ......
哦...
Oh......
呐 呐 呐 ...
Na na na ......
你能想像这样的生活吗：没有爱, 没有自豪, 没有油炸鸡块
Can you imagine no love, pride, deep-fried chicken
即使有时我知道你是错的
Your best friend always sticking up for you
你最好的朋友, 还总是和你站在一起
Even when I know you're wrong
你能想像没有了与爱人的第一次共舞
Can you imagine no first dance
没有了浪漫的情调, 没有了五个小时的电话缠绵
Freeze dried romance five-hour phone conversation
没有了曾经拥有的最好的咖啡, 没有了我
The best soy latte that you ever had and . . . me
You Belong With Me - Taylor Swift
如果你可以看到我才是由始至终都理解你的人
If you could see that I'm the one who understands you
一直陪着你, 为什么你就是不明白
been here all along so why can't you see
你属于我
You belong with me
你正和女朋友聊电话, 她很不高兴
You're on the phone with your girlfriend, she's upset.
她因为你说的某些话而发火
She's going off about something that you said
她不像我, 领会你的幽默感
Cuz she doesn't, get your humor like I do
我在房间里, 又是一个平凡的星期二晚上
I'm in the room, it's a typical Tuesday night
我在听那种她不喜欢的音乐
I'm listening to the kind of music she doesn't like
她不像我对你如此了解
And she'll never know your story like I do
但她穿短裙
She wears short skirts
我穿T恤
I wear T-shirts
她是啦啦队队长
She's cheer captain
而我却坐在露天看台上
And I'm on the bleachers
希望你会有一天醒来发现
Dreaming about the day when you wake up
你理想中的女孩
And find what you're looking for
一直就在你身边
Has been here the whole time
如果你可以看到我才是由始至终都理解你的人
If you could see that I'm the one who understands you
一直陪着你, 为什么你就是不明白
Been here all along so why can't you see
你属于我
You belong with me
你穿着你的旧牛仔裤和我一起在街上闲逛
Walkin' the streets with you and your worn-out jeans
我不禁开始想象, 原本就应该是这样
I can't help thinking this is how it ought to be
在公园长椅上我一边傻笑一边在想
Laughing on a park bench, thinking to myself
嘿, 这居然如此容易
Hey isn't this easy
你的笑容可以照亮整个城镇
And you've got a smile that could light up this whole town
自从她把你抛弃之后我已经有一段时间没有看到了
I haven't seen it in a while since she brought you down
你说你没事
You say you're fine
我知道你应该更加坚强
I know you better then that
嘿, 这样的女孩你为什么还紧追不放
Hey whatcha doing with a girl like that
她穿高跟鞋
She wears high heels
我穿运动鞋
I wear sneakers
她是啦啦队队长
She's cheer captain and
而我却坐在露天看台上
I'm on the bleachers
希望你会有一天醒来发现
Dreaming about the day when you wake up and find
你理想中的女孩
That what you're looking for
一直就在你身边
Has been here the whole time
如果你可以看到我才是由始至终都理解你的人
If you could see that I'm the one who understands you
一直陪着你, 为什么你就是不明白
Been here all along so why can't you see
你属于我
You belong with me
我站在你家的后门口等着你
Standing by and waiting at your back door
一直等着你, 你怎么还不明白
All this time how could you not know
亲爱的
Baby....
你属于我
You belong with me
我想起你开车到我家
I remember you drivin' to my house
在半夜的时候
In the middle of the night
我才是那个当你要哭时
I'm the one who makes you laugh
让你笑的那个人
When you know you're about to cry
我知道你最喜欢的歌
And I know your favorite songs
你也告诉了我你的梦想
And you tell me about your dreams
我想我知道你的归宿
Think I know where you belong
我想你属于我
Think I know it's with me...
你难道看不出我才是由始至终都理解你的人
If you could see that I'm the one who understands you
一直陪着你
Been here all along
为什么你就是不明白
So why can't you see
你属于我
You belong with me
我站在你家的后门口等着你
Standing by and waiting at your back door
一直等着你
All this time
亲爱的你怎么还不明白
How could you not know
亲爱的, 你属于我
Baby you belong with me
你难道看不出我才是由始至终都理解你的人
If you could see that I'm the one who understands you
一直陪着你
Been here all along
为什么你就是不明白
So why can't you see
你属于我
You belong with me
我站在你家的后门口等着你
Standing by and waiting at your back door
一直等着你
All this time
你怎么还不明白
How could you not know
亲爱的, 你属于我
Baby you belong with me
你属于我
You belong with me
你有没有想过也许就是这样
Have you ever thought just maybe
你属于我
You belong with me
Dear John - Taylor Swift
那些我围绕在你周围的夜晚
Long were the nights
是那么的漫长
When my days once revolved around you
低头数着自己的步子
Counting my footsteps
祈祷着, 这一次我的世界不会再次的垮塌
Prayin' the floor won't fall through, again
那时, 妈妈告诫我“我是迷失了自己”
My mother accused me of losing my mind
但是我却对她发誓, 我很好
But I swore I was fine
你为我描绘了一片湛蓝的天空
You paint me a blue sky and go back
转过身时却已是大雨倾盆而下
And turn it to rain
我好像生活在你设计的象棋游戏里
And I lived in your chess game
每一天, 你都会换上新的规则
But you changed the rules every day
我不知道, 今晚电话另一头的
Wonderin which version of you
是哪一个你
I might get on the phone, tonight
我放弃了继续走下去
Well I stopped pickin' up
就让这首歌告诉你为什么
And this song is to let you know why
亲爱的约翰
Dear John
现在, 我知道你已经离开
I see it all now that you're gone
难道你觉得我还太年轻
Don't you think I was too young
还是不碰为好？
To be messed with
一个女孩, 穿着美丽的裙子
The girl in the dress
一路哭泣着朝着家走去
Cried the whole way home
我早应知道
I shoulda known.
也许我应该责怪我
Well maybe it's me
和我那盲目的乐观主义
And my blind optimism to blame
也许我应该责怪你, 还有你那
Maybe its you and your sick need
“给了爱, 然后立刻将爱抽离你心底”的坏习惯
To give love then take it away
你会把我的名字放在
And you'll add my name
那份长长的“背叛者名单里” 吧
To your long list of traitors
我真的不能理解
Who don't understand
回忆当时, 懊悔着
And I'll look back in regret
他们对我的劝告“尽最大努力, 跑得越快越好”
How I ignored when they said
就这样的被我无视
Run as fast as you can
亲爱的约翰
Dear John
现在, 我知道你已经离开
I see it all now that you're gone
难道你觉得我还太年轻
Don't you think I was too young
还是不碰为好？
To be messed with
一个女孩, 穿着美丽的裙子
The girl in the dress
一路哭泣着朝着家走去
Cried the whole way home
亲爱的约翰
Dear John
我知道这一切都是错误
I see it all now it was wrong
难道你不认为19岁真的太年轻
Don't you think nineteen's too young
被邀请进你那黑暗的, 扭曲的游戏吗？
To be played by your dark twisted games
当我如此爱你的时候
When I loved you so
我应该早就知道
I shoulda known
你真的是一个说“对不起”的行家
You are an expert at sorry
让每一字都那么的含糊不清
And keeping lines blurry
我从来没有在你的那些“考察”里
And never impressed by me
给你留下深刻的印象
Acing your tests
那些原本美丽的现在却
All the girls that you run dry
毫无生气的眼睛背后
Have tired lifeless eyes
是你的无情燃尽了她们的泪滴
Cuz you burned them out
在被你烈火般灼伤之前
But I took your matches
我已离开了你的游戏
Before fire could catch me
所以, 现在不要看着有我的方向
So don't look now
我就如烟火般
I'm shining like fireworks
在你悲伤孤独的小镇上空灿烂的绽放着
Over your sad empty town
喔
Oh woah oh
亲爱的约翰
Dear John
现在, 我知道你已经离开
I see it all now that you're gone
难道你觉得我还太年轻
Don't you think I was too young
还是不碰为好？
To be messed with
一个女孩, 穿着美丽的裙子
The girl in the dress
一路哭泣着朝着家走去
Cried the whole way home
现在, 我知道你已经离开
I see it all now that you're gone
难道你觉得我还太年轻
Don't you think I was too young
还是不碰为好？
To be messed with
一个女孩, 穿着美丽的裙子
The girl in the dress
写下一首给你的歌
Wrote you a song
你早就应该知道
You shoulda known
你难道不认为我太年轻了吗？
Don't you think I was too young
你真的应该早就知道
You shoulda known.
Enchanted - Taylor Swift
我在这里, 在这样的夜晚里, 还是一样, 勉强的笑声, 虚伪的微笑
There I was again tonight forcing laughter, faking smiles
那个地方, 也还是一样的, 疲乏而孤单
Same old tired, lonely place
虚伪毫无保留的如铜墙铁壁般将我包围
Walls of insincerity
还是一样, 飘忽不定的眼神, 空空荡荡的房子, 但是就在你出现的那一瞬间, 这一切立即消失的无影无踪
Shifiting eyes and vancancy vanished when I saw your face
我的零零碎碎的词字, 只能拼凑出“我已经对你着了迷 ”
All I can say is it was enchanting to meet you
你的眼睛悄悄向我传达着“我们以前见过吗？”
Your eyes whispered "have we met?"
来自这个拥挤空间的另一个角落, 你完美的侧脸已踏上了通向我心房的道路
Across the room your silhouette starts to make it's way to me
一段俏皮的小交流, 就这样有了开始
The playful conversation starts
回应着你传达的每一个神态, 就好象悄悄的传递着我们秘密的小纸条
Counter all your quick remarks like passing notes in secrecy
那就是, 我已经对你着迷
And it was enchanting to meet you
我的零零碎碎的词字, 只能拼凑出“我已经对你着了迷 ”
All I can say is I was enchanted to meet you
如此绚丽的夜晚, 你会就这样让它成为记忆里的一个片段吗？
This night is sparkling, don't you let it go
我小小的惊讶着, 涨红了脸走在回家的路上
I'm wonderstruck, blushing all the way home
我用了好久好久的时间来猜想, 你是否知道
I'll spend forever wondering if you knew
我已经对你着迷
I was enchanted to meet you
有这样一个问题, 在我脑海里徘徊
The lingering question kept me up
凌晨2点, 谁才是你心中那一个呢？
2 am, who do you love?
我无法将这个问题从我脑海中删去, 直至我完完全全的清醒
I wonder till I'm wide awake
此时, 我正心思不宁的在房间里来来回回的走动
Now I'm pacing back and forth
祈祷着, 此刻, 你就在房门的另一面
Wishing you were at my door
打开门后, 你会对我说
I'd open up and you would say
嗨, 我已经对你着了迷
Hey, it was enchanted to meet you
我现在只知道, 我已经对你着了迷
All I know is I was enchanted to meet you
如此绚丽的夜晚, 你会让它就这样过去吗
This night is sparkling, don't you let it go
我小小的惊讶着, 涨红了脸走在回家的路上
I'm wonderstruck, blushing all the way home
我用了好久好久的时间来猜想, 你是否知道
I'll spend forever wondering if you knew
这个夜晚是如此的完美无瑕, 你会就这样让它成为记忆里的一个片段吗？
This night is flawless, don't you let it go
我小小的惊讶着, 在那里独自跳着舞
I'm wonderstruck, dancing around all alone
我用了好久好久的时间来猜想, 你是否知道
I'll spend forever wondering if you knew
我已经对你着迷
I was enchanted to meet you
我双手合十, 祈祷着这将会成为我们故事的第一页
This is me praying that this was the very first page
而不是这个画上句号前的话语
Not where the story line ends
脑海里不停的回放着你的名字, 直到你再一次出现在我的面前
My thoughts will echo your name until I see you again
这些就是保留在我心底的词句, 就和我马上就要离开的事实一样
These are the words I held back as I was leaving too soon
我已经迷上了你
I was enchanted to meet you
希望你不要爱上别人
Please don't be in love with someone else
希望你不要让我一直等着你
Please don't have somebody waiting on you
希望你不要爱上别人
Please don't be in love with someone else
希望你不要让我一直等着你
Please don't have somebody waiting on you
希望你不要爱上别人
Please don't be in love with someone else
希望你不要让我一直等着你
Please don't have somebody waiting on you
如此绚丽的夜晚, 你会让它就这样过去吗
This night is sparkling, don't you let it go
我小小的惊讶着, 涨红了脸走在回家的路上
I'm wonderstruck, blushing all the way home
我用了好久好久的时间来猜想, 你是否知道
I'll spend forever wondering if you knew
这个夜晚是如此的完美无瑕, 你会就这样让它成为记忆里的一个片段吗？
This night is flawless, don't you let it go
我小小的惊讶着, 在那里独自跳着舞
I'm wonderstruck, dancing around all alone
用了好久好久的时间来猜想, 你是否知道
I'll spend forever wondering if you knew
我已经对你着迷
I was enchanted to meet you
希望你不要让我一直等着你
Please don't have somebody waiting on you
Haunted - Taylor Swift
你, 和我, 走在一条脆弱易碎的道路上
You and I walk a fragile line
其实, 我的心里一直都很清楚
I have known it all this time
但是, 我不曾想到, 我会亲眼见证它的破碎
But I never thought I'd live to see it break
黑暗正慢慢的将我吞噬, 寂静恐怖的将我淹没
It's getting dark and its all too quiet
已经无法相信这一切的一切
And I can't trust anything now
无法弥补的错误, 正在将你包围
And its comin' over you like its all a big mistake
努力的屏住呼吸, 但请不要再迷失你自己了
Oh,holding my breathe, won't lose you again
你的眼睛, 也失去了温暖的光芒
Something's made your eyes go cold
我请求着, 不要就这样把我丢下
Come on, come on don't leave me like this
我以为你已经清楚一切
I thought I had you figured out
有些事情走向了错误的方向, 你曾经是我的世界
Something's gone terribly wrong, you're all I wanted
请求着, 不要就这样离我而去
Come on, come on don't leave me like this
我以为你已经清楚一切
I thought I had you figured out
当你不在身边的时候, 我无法呼吸
Can't breathe whenever you're gone
已经没有办法回到过去, 我饱受着煎熬
Can't turn back now I'm haunted
坐在这里, 脑海里浮现的是我们曾经的一切
Stood there and watched you walk away
眼前却是你渐渐远去的场景
From everything we had
但是, 我对你说过的话, 还是源于我的心底
But I still mean every word I say to you
他, 也许会试着带走我的痛苦
He will try to take away my pain
他, 也许能让我微笑
And he just might make me smile
但是, 我一直都希望, 那个人是你
But the whole time I'm wishin he was you instead
努力的屏住呼吸, 再也不会见到你
Oh, holding my breath, won't see you again
有些事情让我一直犹豫不决
Something keeps me holding on to nothing
我请求着, 不要就这样把我丢下
Come on, come on don't leave me like this
我以为你已经清楚一切
I thought I had you figured out
一些什么事情正走向无法挽回的境界, 你曾经是我的世界
Something's gone terribly wrong, you're all I wanted
请求着, 不要就这样离我而去
Come on, come on don't leave me like this
我以为你已经清楚一切
I thought I had you figured out
当你不在我身边的时候我无法呼吸
Can't breathe whenever you're gone
已经没有办法回到过去, 我饱受着煎熬
Can't turn back now I'm haunted
我知道, 我真的知道, 我一直都知道
I know, I know, I just know
你还没有离开, 你不能就这样离开
You're not gone, you can't be gone
不能就这样离我而去
No
我祈求着, 不要就这样把我丢下
Come on, come on don't leave me like this
我以为你已经清楚一切
I thought I had you figured out
有些事情走向了错误的方向
Something's gone terribly wrong
无法完成那些我们已经揭开的篇章
Won't finish what you started
祈求着, 不要就这样把我丢下
Come on, come on don't leave me like this
我以为你已经清楚一切
I thought I had you figured out
当你离开的时候, 我无法呼吸, 无法回到过去
Can't breathe whenever you're gone can't go back
我饱受着煎熬
I'm haunted
喔, 喔, 喔, 喔, 喔
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh
我们走在一条易碎的道路上
You and I walk a fragile line
一直以来, 我都知道
I have known it all this time
但是我从没想过我会眼看着它破碎
Never ever thought i'd see it break
从没想过, 会是这样
Never thought i'd see it
这张最新的专辑《爱的告白》受到很多东西的启发
This last album "Speak Now" was inspired by a lot of things
都是发生在我的生活当中
that happened to me in my life
但有一首歌受到的启发是
But one thing that inspired the song was um
几年前, 我们进行我们第一次的巡回演唱
we went on our very first headlining tour a few years ago
我曾站在那里
And I used to stand there before
我走上舞台并聆听观众
I would go on stage and listen to the crowd
发出最令人惊奇的尖叫声
making the most amazing magical loud screaming sounds
那就是我说的叫声
That is exactly the sound I'm talking about
然后我听见
And I hear and I
首先我会坐在那然后思考
first of all  I ... I would sit there and think
我不敢相信我在生命当中能够听到那种声音
I can't believe I get to hear that sound one time in my life
然后呢
And uh...
我有这个旋律萦绕在我的脑海
and I would get a melody stuck in my head
这个旋律一直在我脑海中回荡, 直到
And I could never get this melody out of my head until
我最终把它写进一首歌中
I finally wrote it into a song
我把那首歌叫做“万岁”
And uh I called that song "Long Live"
感谢你们为我们呐喊
Thank you so much for screaming for us
这首歌是完全百分之百为你们准备的
This song is so completely a hundred percent for you
Long Live - Taylor Swift
我告诉自己, 要一直记得那一刻
I say remember this moment
印刻在脑海里
In the back of my mind
那时的我们, 站在那里, 不停地挥动手臂
The time we stood with our shaking hands
看台的人群, 开始疯狂起来
The crowds in stands went wild
曾经, 我们是王国里的国王与王后
We were the kings and the queens
他们呼喊着我们的名字
And they read off our names
繁星下, 你的舞步向我诉说着
The night you danced like you knew our lives
我们的生活会就此改写
Would never be the same
你扬起你的头, 好似英雄一般
You held your head like a hero
在史册的那一页
On a history book page
这, 是一个年代的末篇
It was the end of a decade
却是一个新时代的开始
But the start of an age
万岁！ 那些我们并肩穿越的困难艰险
Long live the walls we crashed through
王国的光芒如此耀眼, 只因为你和我
All the kingdom lights shined just for me and you
我在大声呼喊着, “万岁, 那些我们一起创造的奇迹“
I was screaming, long live all the magic we made
就让那些虚伪的人, 冲我们来吧
And bring on all the pretenders
总有一天, 我们会被世人铭记
One day we will be remembered
我告诉自己, 要记得这感受
I said remember this feeling
传阅着这些照片
I passed the pictures around
照片里的我们, 站在角落里等待着
Of all the years that we stood there on the sidelines
祈祷着这一刻的来临
Wishing for right now
这时, 我们是这个世界的统治者
We are the kings and the queens
你, 用你的棒球帽交换了一顶皇冠
You traded your baseball cap for a crown
当他们授予我们奖杯的那一刻
When they gave us our trophies
我们将它高举过头顶
And we held them up for our town
愤世嫉俗的人暴跳如雷
And the cynics were outraged
惊声尖叫着：这实在是荒谬可笑！
Screaming, this is absurd
因为那些穿着带有破洞牛仔裤的小偷们
Cause for a moment a band of thieves
曾经统治着这个世界
In ripped up jeans got to rule the world
万岁！ 那些我们并肩穿越的困难艰险
Long live the walls we crashed through
王国的光芒如此耀眼, 只因为你和我
All the kingdom lights shined just for me and you
我大声呼喊着：万岁, 那些我们一起创造的奇迹
I was screaming, long live all the magic we made
就让那就虚伪的人, 冲着我们来吧
And bring on all the pretenders
我无所畏惧
I'm not afraid
万岁！那些我们一起挪移的山峦
Long live all the mountains we moved
我生命中的那一段时间
I had the time of my life
曾和你一起与邪恶战斗
Fighting dragons with you
我大声呼喊着：就让那一刻的微笑, 一直在你的脸颊
I was screaming, long live the look on your face
就让那些虚伪的人, 冲着我们来吧
And bring on all the pretenders
有一天, 我们会被世人铭记
One day we will be remembered
坚持住, 直到那一刻, 世界为你旋转
Hold on to spinning around
五彩缤纷的纸屑, 漫天飞舞
Confetti falls to the ground
就让记忆里的美好, 扶持着我们, 不再坠落
May these memories break our fall
我们非常喜欢在你们城里游玩
We have absolutely loved spending time in your town
你们是如此的让人惊讶
And you've been so amazing to us
我是说你们知道每一句歌词, 你们整个晚上都在跳舞
I mean you guys know every single word and you've danced this entire night
这对我和台上每个人来说意味着一切
And it means the world to me and every single person you see on stage
谢谢你们
Thank you
你用一点点的时间
And you take a moment
向我起誓
And promise me this:
一直站在我的身边, 哪怕是沧海桑田
That you'll stand by me forever
但是, 如果有一天, 上帝阻止了命运的脚步
But if god forbid fate should step in
将我们的结局改写为“再也不见”
And force us into a goodbye
也许在未来的某一天, 你有了孩子
If you have children someday
当他们指着这些照片的时候
When they point to the pictures
请告诉他们, 我的名字
Please tell them my name
告诉他们, 那时, 人群是如何的开始疯狂
Tell them how the crowds went wild
告诉他们 , 我是多希望, 他们能够闪亮
Tell them how I hope they shine
万岁！那些我们一起穿越的困难
Long live the walls we crashed through
曾经, 我与你分享着生命
I had the time of my life with you
万万岁！那些我们一起穿越的困难
Long, long live the walls we crashed through
那个王国的光芒如此耀眼, 只因为你和我
All the candlelight shined just for me and you
我曾经放声大喊：万岁, 那些我们一起创造的奇迹
And I was screaming, long live all the magic we made
就让那就虚伪的人们, 冲着我们来吧
And bring on all the pretenders
我无所畏惧
I'm not afraid
吟唱着：万岁, 那些我们一起挪移的山峦
Singing long live all the mountains we moved
我曾经和你一起
I had the time of my life
与邪恶战斗
Fighting dragons with you
万万岁！你脸上的神情
Long, long live the look on your face
就让那些虚伪的人们, 冲着来吧
And bring on all the pretenders
总有一天, 我们会被世人铭记
One day we will be remembered
我禁不住注意到, 今晚这是一群有着非常闪耀的亮光的观众
I can't help but notice this is a very sparkly glittery crowds tonight
我觉得
I think...
我看见有些人带了些很亮的东西
I see some of you brought things light up
不如每个有手机或者手电筒的人
What if what if everybody who has like a cellphone or
我不知道谁随身携带手电筒
flashlight. I don't know who carries around a flashlight
如果你带了的话
But if you do
你们能为我把它高高举起吗？
could you put it up in the air for me?
噢, 真好看
Oh that's pretty
你知道有件事
You know the thing
关于人生的事就是每次你学到新的一课
the thing about life is that every time you learn a new lesson
在附近, 总会有另一个等着你
There is just another one right around the corner
你永远都不会知道所有的事
You know, you never know everything
我觉得对我来时, 我有点放弃, 就像
I think you know for me I just kind of giving up and I'm like
跟我将要知道的相比, 我现在一无所知
I know nothing compared to what I'm going to know some day
不久前我就没有觉得我懂得每件事了
And uh I stoped thinking I knew everything a while ago
我觉得最后一次我认为我懂得每件事是在十五岁的时候
I think last time I thought I knew everything I was uh... fifteen
Fifteen - Taylor Swift
你做完深呼吸, 穿过了门
You take a deep breath and you walk through the doors
这是你开学第一天的早晨
It's the morning of your very first day
你向那些新朋友们打招呼
You say hi to your friends you ain't seen in a while
试着与每个人好好相处
Try and stay out of everybodys way
你才刚刚一年级, 你将在这里
It's your freshman year and you're gonna be here
在这个小镇度过接下来的四年
For the next four years in this town
心里偷偷盼望着哪个高年级男生瞧过来对你说：
Hoping one of those senior boys will wink at you and say
“我以前怎么没在这一带见过你？”
You know I haven't seen you around before
因为当你还是十五岁, 有人告诉你他们爱你
Cause when you're fifteen and somebody tells you they love you
你会全然相信
You gonna believe them
当你还是十五岁
And when you're fifteen
就感觉没有什么是需要琢磨的
Feeling like there's nothing to figure out
只需要数到十, 就会信以为真
Well count to ten, take it in
这就是在你知道你是谁之前那十五岁的青春
This is life before you know who you're gonna be at fifteen
你坐在班级里, 挨着一个叫阿比盖尔的红发女孩
You sit in class next to a redhead named Abigail
不用多久你们就成了最好的朋友
And soon enough you're best friends
嘲笑着那些自以为魅压群芳的女孩
Laughing at the other girls who think they're so cool
我们总是想着尽早离开这里
We'll be out of here as soon as we can
而后你有了你人生的初次约会, 他开来一辆车
And then you're on your very first date and he's got a car
你就感觉像是在飞
And you're feeling like flying
妈妈在焦虑地等候, 而你却已相信他就是你的唯一
And your mama's waiting up and you think he's the one
你们在屋子里彻夜狂欢
And you're dancing round your room when the night ends
彻夜地
When the night ends
因为当你还是十五岁, 有人告诉你他们爱你
Cause when you're fifteen and somebody tells you they love you
你会全然相信
You gonna believe them
当你还是十五岁, 你的初吻
And when you're fifteen and your first kiss
会让你飘若天仙
Makes your head spin round well
在你的人生里有着比/和橄榄球队的男孩约会更重要的事情
In your life you'll do things greater than dating the boy on the football team
但在十五岁, 我不曾懂得
I didnt know it at fifteen
你曾等着满足自己所有的愿望和幻想
When all you wanted was to be wanted
真希望现在的你回到过去告诉自己是多么天真
Wish you could go back and tell yourself what you know now
那时我曾发誓有一天要嫁给他
Back then I swore I was gonna marry him someday
但后来我又发现了自己更重要的梦想
But I realized some bigger dreams of mine
而阿比盖尔则把自己拥有的一切都给了一个男孩
Abigail gave everything she had to a boy
一个最后变了心的男孩。我们相拥而泣...
Who changed his mind and we both cried
因为当你还是十五岁, 别人告诉你有人爱你
Cause when you're fifteen and somebody tells you they love you
你会全然相信
You gonna believe them
当你还是十五岁, 不要忘记在跌倒之前看看脚下的路
And when you're fifteen, don't forget to look before you fall
我发现时间可以治愈好一切
But I've found that time can heal most anything
而且你还可以发现曾经你会变成什么样的人
And you just might find who you're supposed to be
而在十五岁时, 我不曾知晓这个答案
I didn't know who I was supposed to be at fifteen
啦...
La la la la la ... la la la la la ... La la la la la...
这是你的第一天
Your very first day
深呼吸, 女孩
You take a deep breath girl
做着深呼吸勇敢地穿过那些门
Take a deep breath as you walk through the doors.
啦...
La la la la la ... la la la la la ... La la la la la...
这是你的第一天
Your very first day
Love Story - Taylor Swift
第一次见到你时, 我们都很年轻
We were both young when I first saw you
闭上眼睛, 即回到过去
I close my eyes and the flashback starts
夏天的夜风中我站在那里, 站在露台上
I'm standing there on a balcony in summer air
看着闪烁的灯光, 看着舞会, 看着裙摆舞动
See the lights, see the party, the ball gowns
看到你穿过人群
See you make your way through the crowd
并说你好, 我不知道
And say hello, little did I know
你就是罗密欧, 你扔着小石子
That you were Romeo, you were throwing pebbles
我爹爹嚷嚷：“不要招惹朱丽叶！”
And my daddy said stay away from Juliet
我在楼梯上哭泣, 请求你不要走
And I was crying on the staircase, begging you please don't go
我说：
And I said
“罗密欧, 带我走, 去一个我们可以独处的地方
Romeo take me somewhere we can be alone
我会一直等你, 我们能做的只能是离开（私奔, 呵呵……）
I'll be waiting, all there's left to do is run
你是我的王子, 我是你的公主
You'll be the prince and I'll be this princess
这是一个爱情故事
It's a love story
宝贝, 只需说, 我愿意”
Baby, just say yes
于是我溜到花园里去见你
So I sneak out to the garden to see you
我们轻轻悄悄, 因为如果被人们发现, 我们只有死路一条
We keep quiet cause we've dead if they knew
所以闭上你的双眼, 暂时逃离此地
So close your eyes, escape this town for a little while
喔, 喔, 喔
Oh, oh, oh
因为你是罗密欧, 我是一个红字
Cause you were Romeo, I was a scarlet letter
而我爹爹又说了：“不要招惹朱丽叶！”
And my daddy said stay away from Juliet
但你是我的一切, 我请求你不要离开我
But you were everything of me, I was begging you please don't go
我说：
And I said
“罗密欧, 带我走, 去一个我们可以独处的地方
Romeo take me somewhere we can be alone
我会一直等你, 我们能做的只能是离开（私奔, 呵呵……）
I'll be waiting, all there's left to do is run
你是我的王子, 我是你的公主
You'll be the prince and I'll be the princess
这是一个爱情故事
It's a love story
宝贝, 只需说, 我愿意”
Baby, just say yes
“罗密欧, 救救我, 试着告诉我如何去感受
Romeo save me try to tell me how it feels
这份爱很艰辛, 但很真实
This love is difficult, but it's so real
不要害怕, 我们会理出头绪
Don't be afraid we'll make it out of this mess
这是一个爱情故事
It's a love story
宝贝, 只需说, 我愿意”
Baby, just say yes
我厌倦了等待, 总在想, 你是否还会回来
I got tired of waiting, wondering if you were ever coming around
我对你的信念正渐渐消逝
My faith in you was fading
在镇外遇见你时
When I met you on the outskirts of town
我说：
And I said
“罗密欧, 救救我, 我觉得非常孤独
Romeo save me I've been feeling so alone
我一直等你, 但你却全不露面
I'll keep waiting for you but you never come
这是否是我的空想, 我完全不知道作何感想”
Is this in my head, I don't know what to think
他跪在地上, 拿出一枚戒指
He knelt to the ground and pulled out a ring
并说道：
And said
“嫁给我吧, 朱丽叶, 你再也不会孤独
Marry me Juliet you'll never have to be alone
我爱你, 这便是我确知的全部
I love you and that's all I really know
我跟你爹爹谈过了, 去挑一件婚纱吧
I talked to your dad you'll pick out a white dress
这是我们的爱情故事
It's a love story
宝贝, 只需说, 我愿意”
Baby, just say yes
喔, 喔
Oh, oh
我们相识时, 彼此都很年轻
We were both young when I first saw you
我爱你们
I love you
98场演出, 17个国家, 3个大洲
《爱的告白》环球巡演2011
致谢：
这张专辑献给那些在巡演中或坐, 或站, 一同陪伴我的美好而善良的人们, 因为有了你们的存在, 我的巡演被装点得更加美丽。致那些不可思议的人们, 谢谢你们陪我度过这段时光
“我觉得你不应该等下去, 你应该现在就说出来”